Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Haupt, Irene
8 CD-ROMS (142 digital images in tiff and jpeg format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 142 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo Festival 2009 at the University at Buffalo.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2009.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2009 is available in the University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009 contains 142 images of participants in the festival for 2009. The list of musicians includes David Felder, Brad Lubman, Stefano Scodanibbio, Bernard Rands, Harvey Sollberger, Lina Bahn, Mathew Rosenblum, Philippe Manoury, Christophe Desjardins, James Baker, Mario Caroli, Mikko Luoma, and the Meridian Arts Ensemble.
Arrangement
Six series, one for each of the original CD-ROMs. Series titles are either transcriptions of titles on corresponding contact sheets.
I. CD-ROM 1. Mikko Luoma JIB 2009
II. CD-ROM 2. Inner sky JIB2009
III. CD-ROM 3. Masterclasses JIB 2009
IV. CD-ROM 4. Stefano Scodanibbio JIB 2009
V. CD-ROM 5. NY New Music Ensemble JIB 2009
VI. CD-ROM 6. June in Buffalo 2009
Container List
- Mikko Luoma, JIB 2009, June 2009, I.; 1 CD-ROM (14 image files in TIFF format)
  Files are numerically arranged by intermediate, assigned file names.
  - Mikko Luoma with his accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_01)
  - Mikko Luoma in his accordion workshop in Baird hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_02)
  - Mikko Luoma playing his accordion, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_03)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_04)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_05)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_06)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_07)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_08)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_09)
  - Mikko Luoma, accordionist, with June in Buffalo student, Moshe Shulman, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_10)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_11)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall with Harvey Sollberger and Bernard Rands in audience, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_12)
  - Mikko Luoma playing accordion in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_13)
  - Mikko Luoma talking during his accordion workshop in Baird Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_01_14)
- Inner Sky, JIB 2009, June 2009, II.; 1 CD-ROM (44 image files in TIFF format)
  - Mario Caroli playing piccolo with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_01)
  - Mario Caroli playing piccolo with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in rehearsal of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_02)
  - Mario Caroli playing piccolo with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_03)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_04)
  - Composer David Felder shaking hand of flute soloist Mario Caroli, after performance of Felder's Inner Sky by the Slee Sinfonietta with conductor Brad Lubman, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_05)
  - Composer David Felder accepting applause after performance of his Inner Sky, by flutist Mario Caroli with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_06)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_07)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_08)
  - Flutist Mario Caroli during performance with the Slee Sinfonietta of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_09)
  - Mario Caroli playing piccolo with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_10)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in rehearsal of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_11)
  - Composer David Felder shaking hands with conductor Brad Lubman after performance of Felder's Inner Sky by flutist Mario Caroli with the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_12)
  - Mario Caroli playing piccolo with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_13)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_14)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_15)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_16)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta and conductor Brad Lubman taking bows after performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_17)
  - Percussionist Jon Hepfer bowing glockenspiel during rehearsal with the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_18)
  - Percussionist Jon Hepfer bowing glockenspiel during performance with Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_19)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist rehearsing David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_20)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_21)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_22)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_23)
  - String section of the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_24)
  - String section of the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_25)
  - Pianist Catarina Domenici and percussionist Rin Ozaki performing with the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_26)
  - Violinists in the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_27)
  - Flutist Mario Caroli, conductor Brad Lubman, and composer David Felder consult during a rehearsal of Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_28)
  - Flutist Mario Caroli, conductor Brad Lubman, and composer David Felder consult during a rehearsal of Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_29)
  - Concertmaster Charles Haupt and other string players of the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_30)
  - Concertmaster Charles Haupt and other string players of the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_31)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman and composer David Felder on edge of stage in Slee Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_32)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_33)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_34)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_35)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_36)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, taking bow in front of the Slee Sinfonietta after performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_37)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_38)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, with Rin Ozaki percussion, in rehearsal of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_39)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, at rehearsal of David Felder's Inner Sky with the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_40)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, at performance of David Felder's Inner Sky with the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_41)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_42)
  - Mario Caroli, flutist, with the Slee Sinfonietta conducted by Brad Lubman in performance of David Felder's Inner Sky, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_43)
  - Percussionist Tom Kolor in performance with the Slee Sinfonietta, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_02_44)
- Masterclasses, JIB 2009, June 2009, III.; 1 CD-ROM (31 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Bernard Rands with June in Buffalo student Kye Ryung Park, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_01)
  - Composer Mathew Rosenblum with June in Buffalo students Todd Tarantino, Chun Ting Pang, Christopher Rogerson, Jason Thompson, and Joseph Lake, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_02)
  - Composer Mathew Rosenblum during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_03)
  - Composer David Felder with students Andrew Ly, Christian Gentry, Matthew Schreibeis, Todd Tarantino, and Eleanor Aversa during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_04)
  - Composer David Felder with students Andrew Ly, Christian Gentry, Matthew Schreibeis, Todd Tarantino, and Eleanor Aversa during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_05)
  - Composer David Felder with students Andrew Ly, Christian Gentry, Matthew Schreibeis, Todd Tarantino, and Eleanor Aversa during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_06)
  - Composer David Felder during a lecture at June in Buffalo, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_07)
  - Composer Harvey Sollberger during lecture at June in Buffalo, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_08)
  - Composer Harvey Sollberger during lecture at June in Buffalo, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_09)
  - June in Buffalo student composer, Jaime S. Reveles, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_10)
  - June in Buffalo student composer Jason Thompson, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_11)
  - Group photograph of the June in Buffalo student composers for 2009, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_12)
  - Composer David Felder with students Andrew Ly, Christian Gentry, Matthew Schreibeis, Todd Tarantino, and Eleanor Aversa during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_13)
  - Composer Bernard Rands during masterclass with June in Buffalo students, Moshe Shulman, Diane Berry, Helena Michelson, and Chun Ting Pang, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_14)
  - Composer David Felder with students Andrew Ly, Christian Gentry, Matthew Schreibeis, Todd Tarantino, and Eleanor Aversa during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_15)
  - Composer David Felder with students Andrew Ly, Christian Gentry, Matthew Schreibeis, Todd Tarantino, and Eleanor Aversa during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_16)
  - Composer Martin Bresnick with students Moshe Shulman and Matthew Schreibeis during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_17)
  - Composer Mathew Rosenblum with students Chun Ting Pang, Joseph Lake, Jason Thompson, and Christopher Rogerson during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_18)
  - Composer Brian Griffeath-Loeb during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_19)
  - Composer Bernard Rands during masterclass with June in Buffalo students, Moshe Shulman, Diane Berry, Helena Michelson, and Chun Ting Pang, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_20)
  - Composer Harvey Sollberger with students Andrew Ly, John Bacon, Helena Michelson, and Eric Lindsay during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_21)
  - Composer Harvey Sollberger with students Andrew Ly, John Bacon, and Eric Lindsay during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_22)
  - Composer Mathew Rosenblum with students Chun Ting Pang, Joseph Lake, Jason Thompson, and Christopher Rogerson during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_23)
  - Composer Harvey Sollberger with students Andrew Ly, John Bacon, Helena Michelson, and Eric Lindsay during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_24)
  - Composer Mathew Rosenblum during June in Buffalo masterclass, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_25)
  - June in Buffalo student composers Eric Lindsay, Christian Gentry, and Travis Alford, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_26)
  - June in Buffalo student composer Jason Thompson, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_27)
  - Group photograph of the June in Buffalo student composers for 2009, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_28)
  - June in Buffalo student composers Chun Ting Pang, Joseph Lake, Jason Thompson, and Christopher Rogerson studying scores, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_29)
  - June in Buffalo student composer Sara Carvalho, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_30)
  - June in Buffalo student composers Diana Soh and Moshe Shulman, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_03_31)
- Stefano Scodanibbio, JIB 2009, June 2009, IV.; 1 CD-ROM (5 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer and double bass player Stefano Scodanibbio during June in Buffalo workshop, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_04_01)
  - Composer and double bass player Stefano Scodanibbio during June in Buffalo workshop, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_04_02)
  - Composer and double bass player Stefano Scodanibbio during June in Buffalo workshop, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_04_03)
  - Composer and double bass player Stefano Scodanibbio during June in Buffalo workshop, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_04_04)
  - Composer and double bass player Stefano Scodanibbio during June in Buffalo workshop, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_04_05)
- NY New Music Ensemble, JIB 2009 June 2009, V.; 1 CD-ROM (10 image files in TIFF format)
  - Conductor James Baker in rehearsal with violoncellist Chris Finckel, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_01)
  - Conductor James Baker in rehearsal with the New York New Music Ensemble, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_02)
  - June in Buffalo student composer Eric Lindsay rehearsing with violoncellist Chris Finckel, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_03)
  - June in Buffalo student composer Eric Lindsay at rehearsal in Slee Hall, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_04)
  - Conductor James Baker rehearsing with violinist Linda Quan, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_05)
  - Conductor James Baker with June in Buffalo student composer Mark Fromm, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_06)
  - James Baker conducting New York New Music Ensemble members, Linda Quan, Chris Finckel, Jean Kopperud, and pianist Stephen Gosling, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_07)
  - James Baker conducting New York New Music Ensemble members, Linda Quan, Chris Finckel, Jean Kopperud, and pianist Stephen Gosling, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_08)
  - Conductor James Baker rehearsing with the New York New Music Ensemble, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_09)
  - Conductor James Baker rehearsing with the New York New Music Ensemble, Stephen Gosling, piano and Tom Kolor, percussion, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_05_10)
- June in Buffalo 2009, June 2009, VI.; 1 CD-ROM (38 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Philippe Manoury with violist Christophe Desjardins, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_01)
  - Composer Philippe Manoury with violist Christophe Desjardins, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_02)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley in performance of Bernard Rands Now again, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_03)
  - June in Buffalo student composer Bruce Pennycook, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_04)
  - Robert Franz conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic in June in Buffalo rehearsal, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_05)
  - Robert Franz conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic in June in Buffalo rehearsal, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_06)
  - Robert Franz conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic in June in Buffalo rehearsal, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_07)
  - Violist Christophe Desjardins, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_08)
  - Violist Christophe Desjardins in rehearsal, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_09)
  - Violist Christophe Desjardins, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_10)
  - Violist Christophe Desjardins in action, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_11)
  - Composer Bernard Rands accepting applause after performance of his Now again, with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, conductor Brad Lubman, and the Slee Sinfonietta on stage, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_12)
  - Composer David Felder discussing his piece Another Face with violinist Lina Bahn, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_13)
  - Composer David Felder with violinist Lina Bahn, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_14)
  - Composer Mathew Rosenblum, with conductor Brad Lubman, composer David Felder, and violinist Lina Bahn, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_15)
  - Composers Steve Antosca and Mathew Rosenblum, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_16)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman, composer David Felder, and violist Sandy Robbins, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_17)
  - Flutist Lindsey Goodman performing Mathew Rosenblum's Under the rainbow, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_18)
  - Composer Philippe Manoury and violist Christophe Desjardins, with Christophe Lebreton and unidentified sound engineer at sound console, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_19)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta, with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley in performance of Bernard Rands Now again, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_20)
  - Violist Christophe Desjardins, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_21)
  - Violinist Lina Bahn, June 2009, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2009_06_22)